[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the reason for the crash of West Caribbean Airways Flight 708 in Venezuela on August 16, 2005?", "correct_answer": "Engine trouble", "incorrect_answers": ["Running out of fuel", "Bomb explosion", "Hijacking"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How large can Jupiter appear in the Earths sky?", "correct_answer": "50 arcseconds", "incorrect_answers": ["35 arcseconds", "55 arcseconds", "40 arcseconds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Travis Metcalfe, an astronomer at the Harvard-Smithsonian Center for Astrophysics, has presented a fascinating theory: he believes the largest diamond known is located where?", "correct_answer": "In a near star\u2019s core", "incorrect_answers": ["In Earth\u2019s core", "On the moon\u2019s dark side", "At the bottom of the Mariana Trench"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which was the first racehorse to run the Kentucky Derby in less than 2 minutes?", "correct_answer": "Secretariat", "incorrect_answers": ["Cigar", "Man OWar", "Seabiscuit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What US state borders the states of Virginia, Kentucky, Ohio, Pennsylvania and Maryland?", "correct_answer": "West Virginia", "incorrect_answers": ["Tennessee", "Virginia", "North Carolina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the literal meaning of the Japanese word Chairo which denotes a brown color?", "correct_answer": "Tea color", "incorrect_answers": ["Earth color", "Chestnut color", "Wood color"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What phobia does Detective John Scottie Ferguson have in Alfred Hitchcocks 1958 masterpiece Vertigo?", "correct_answer": "Acrophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Arachnophobia", "Bacteriophobia", "Claustrophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the occupation of Dolly Partons character, Truvy Jones, in the 1989 comedy-drama movie Steel Magnolias?", "correct_answer": "Beautician", "incorrect_answers": ["Singer", "Cook", "Seamstress"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mel Brooks shot in color the entire film Young Frankenstein.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What event came last in the CGI blockbuster movie The Day After Tomorrow?", "correct_answer": "The blizzards", "incorrect_answers": ["The tornadoes", "The flood", "The hurricanes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This play was written by Shakespeare on the request of Queen Elizabeth I.", "correct_answer": "The Merry Wives of Windsor", "incorrect_answers": ["Much Ado About Nothing", "The Tempest", "Henry VIII"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does liquid mercury float on liquid gold?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}]